{"data":[{"question":"We are both ________ doctors.","a":"the","b":"a","c":"an","d":"no article","answer":"4","explain":"\n- If common noun is in the form of plural noun, it will not take any articles","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"This is ________ ink pot.","a":"the","b":"a","c":"an","d":"no article","answer":"3","explain":"\n- A\/an: used when you are mentioning a person or a thing for the first time\n- An is used when the next word begins with a vowel sound","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"They are ________ tall.","a":"the","b":"a","c":"an","d":"no article","answer":"4","explain":"- We don't use any articles before adjectives","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Hoa is ________ good pupil.","a":"the","b":"a","c":"an","d":"no article","answer":"2","explain":"\n- A\/an: used to show that you are referring to a general type of person or thing and not a specific person or thin.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"That is a bag. It is on ________ table.","a":"the","b":"a","c":"an","d":"no article","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The: used to show that you are talking about a particular thing or person that has already been mentioned, is already known about, or is the only one.\u00a0\n+ On: the position is already defined.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"We are in ________ same class.","a":"the","b":"a","c":"an","d":"no article","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The same\/the same as: used to say that two or more people or things are exactly like each.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Your book is ________ the desk.","a":"at","b":"over","c":"on","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":"\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on \n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk... \n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry... \n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page... \n- Over:above or higher than something, without touching it.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"My pens and pencils are ________ the table.","a":"at","b":"over","c":"on","d":"between","answer":"3","explain":"\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on \n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk... \n- Between for something in or through the space that separates two things.\u00a0\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page... \n- Over:above or higher than something, without touching it.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"My family's picture is ________ the wall.","a":"at","b":"over","c":"on","d":"opposite","answer":"3","explain":"\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on \n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk... \n- Opposite:if one thing or person is opposite another, they are facing each other.\u00a0\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page... \n- Over:above or higher than something, without touching it.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Lan and Lien are ________ the desk.","a":"at","b":"in","c":"on","d":"into","answer":"1","explain":"\n- At: sitting or standing close to something, especially in order to do something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"}]}